<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Help Wanted</title>
<description>Help Wanted Issues</description>
<link>https://lbonanomi.github.io/workspace/feed.xml</link>
<item>	<title>Move from AppVeyor to GitHub Actions</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/certstore/issues/19</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>This file should be migrated to GitHub Actions: https://github.com/github/certstore/blob/main/.appveyor.yml"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>license yaml format issue</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/choosealicense.com/issues/758</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>The <code>using</code> part of the license.txt looks weird to me. It’s an array of single-element map like thisrn<code>yamlrnusing:rn  - youtube-dl: https://github.com/rg3/youtube-dl/blob/master/LICENSErn  - kakoune: https://github.com/mawww/kakoune/blob/master/UNLICENSErn  - RDF.rb: https://github.com/ruby-rdf/rdf/blob/master/UNLICENSErn</code>rnwhy not just use a single map like thisrn<code>yamlrnusing:rn  youtube-dl: https://github.com/rg3/youtube-dl/blob/master/LICENSErn  kakoune: https://github.com/mawww/kakoune/blob/master/UNLICENSErn  RDF.rb: https://github.com/ruby-rdf/rdf/blob/master/UNLICENSErn</code>rnor an array of structered maprn<code>yamlrnusing:rn  - name: youtube-dlrn    url: https://github.com/rg3/youtube-dl/blob/master/LICENSErn  - name: kakounern    url: https://github.com/mawww/kakoune/blob/master/UNLICENSErn  - name: RDF.rbrn    url: https://github.com/ruby-rdf/rdf/blob/master/UNLICENSErn</code>rnIt makes the deserialise code boilerplate, for e.g in Rust I have to declare this field like rn<code>Rustrnusing: Option&lt;Vec&lt;HashMap&lt;String, String&gt;&gt;&gt;,rn</code>rnWhen using this <code>using</code> field, I have to iterate the vector, during which I have to iterate the single-element map!rnIn other formats, it would bern<code>Rustrnusing: Option&lt;HashMap&lt;String, String&gt;&gt;,rn</code>rnorrn<code>Rustrnusing: Option&lt;Vec&lt;SomeStruct&gt;&gt;,rn</code>"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Test that license texts match SPDX plain license texts</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/choosealicense.com/issues/636</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>We should have a test that each license text in <code>_licenses</code> is the same as the plain text license in the SPDX collection to automate the requirement described at https://github.com/github/choosealicense.com/blob/gh-pages/CONTRIBUTING.md#adding-a-licensernrn&gt; The text of the license should match the corresponding text found in <a href="https://github.com/spdx/license-list-data/blob/master/text/">spdx/license-list-data</a>. If there are errors there, please fix them in <a href="https://github.com/spdx/license-list-XML">spdx/license-list-XML</a> (from which the plain text version is generated) so as to minimize license text variation and make it easier for choosealicense.com to eventually consume license texts directly from SPDX.rnrnThe test could clone spdx/license-list-data and compare each license we have cataloged in this project. Many existing licenses would probably have to be marked as expected failures due to bugs in SPDX output and discrepancies in how this project has cataloged some licenses. But we should address upfront for any new license cataloged here, and continue to chip away at the existing inconsistencies."</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>I18N</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/choosealicense.com/issues/68</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Would love to see about baking in I18N support to choosealicense.com proper. See #67 and #62nnWe already have the bulk of the strings in a single file (<code>_config.yml</code>), so it should just be a matter of abstracting out some of our variables, as far as I can tell.nnWould love to take this on starting in August if there’s interest. Would be a great exercise to set a standard for Jekyll L10N, and can iterate on some of the lessons learned form https://github.com/CMSgov/healthcare.gov.nn@parkr any interest?n@dhcole any insight / words of wisdom?n"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Support for locally present bundles</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/codeql-action/issues/154</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>I would like to run code-scanning with a custom code-scanning bundlernthat already is present on my local disk. I can currently do that byrnmaking the following hack:rnrn### 1 Install bundle in tool cache:rnrnUse <code>toolCache.cacheDir</code> to install the bundle with a specially crafted ID:rnrn<code>jsrntc.cacheDir(localBundlePath, 'CodeQL', "0.0.0-XXX-DUMMY-BUNDLE-ID");rn</code>rnrn### 2 Convince codeql to look in the tool cache:rnrnThe codeql action is then invoked with a dummy URL that will make codeql.ts lookup the bundle with the specially crafted ID:rnrn<code>yamlrn        ...rn        tools: dummy://codeql-bundle-XXX-DUMMY-BUNDLE-ID/dummyrn        ...rn</code>rnrn—rnrnThis works, but I would like a more reliable solution. I am not surernwhat the best approach is for supporting my use case, but I am happyrnto look into implementing a suggestion.rn"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>TODO: Configure caching for fast building on CI</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/government.github.com/issues/750</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Description and details here: https://github.com/gjtorikian/html-proofer#configuring-caching and https://github.com/gjtorikian/html-proofer#caching-with-travis"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Dockerfile support</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/licensed/issues/272</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Would be great if <code>licensed</code> supported analyzing <code>Dockerfile</code>s and what is installed there to track all dependencies of a project!"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>List of languages without a colour</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/linguist/issues/5003</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Continuing from #4506. 49<item>	<title>Proposal: Make triaging more welcoming to external contributors</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/linguist/issues/4982</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>I’ve contributed on and off to linguist since 2017 and over time I’ve observed a quite frustrating pattern with issues and pull requests: legitimate issues and pull requests get labelled quite quickly as stale (30 days) and then closed (60), with no further option to reopen them.rnrnI understand that this workflow may be convenient for maintainers, but it seems discouraging in a few ways:rnrn- For a casual contributor, 60 days may be a too strict deadline for a Pull Request. It is quite frustrating to come back at a Pull Request a couple of months later (holidays or whatever reason for inactivity) to find you need to create a new one. rnrn- For issues, closing an issue just because there is no PR in 60 days hides them from people who are looking for active ways to contribute. It also tends to promote filing duplicates without reading any of the previous discussion.rnrnI think this could be improved in a way that promotes external contributions while maintaining convenience for maintainers. There are probably many good ways, but I’m thinking about something along the following lines:rnrn- Pull Requests: Do not close them automatically (or extend the grace period). There’s 73 PRs closed as Stale over a ~2 years period. A few of them were mostly ready, so the project could probably benefit from keeping them alive for a while.rnrn- Issues: Once an issue is confirmed to be a valid bug or feature request, add a label (e.g. <code>Help Wanted</code>) and exclude it from the Stale workflow. This label would be a great way for people looking to contribute, while making it clear to the reporter that it needs someone to work on it. Keeping them open and clearly marked also makes them more easily discoverable by users experiencing the same issue, so they can contribute to the discussion.rnrnWhat do you think?"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Investigate semantic-rust macro tests</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/semantic/issues/553</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p><span class="citation" data-cites="p-alik">@p-alik</span> has graciously added the <code>semantic-rust</code> package but we’ve had to exclude some macro corpus tests due to parsing issues.rnrnSee https://github.com/github/semantic/pull/551 for details."</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Move from Travis CI and Appveyor to GitHub Actions</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/smimesign/issues/71</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>The following files are historical artifacts:rnrn- Travis CI for macOS builds: https://github.com/github/smimesign/blob/main/.travis.ymlrn- AppVeyor for Windows builds: https://github.com/github/smimesign/blob/main/.appveyor.ymlrnrnIn fact, the macOS build doesn’t upload releases anymore.rnrnBoth of these should be moved to GitHub Actions. I have a test branch for macOS at:rnhttps://github.com/github/smimesign/tree/macos-buildrnrnThis is not a high priority for us, but if someone took the time to migrate and debug the CI files for GH Actions it would help us maintain this project!"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Don't connect to kext when invoked with CLI args</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/SoftU2F/issues/39</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>We try to connect to the kext when the app starts (<a href="https://github.com/github/SoftU2F/blob/45825a5bd6e6bad7ae9bd681c8584cbcb6e7fb7b/SoftU2FTool/U2FHID.swift#L24">code</a>). This also happens when the app is launched from the command line (Eg. for deleting/listing registrations). If the app is already running in the background we’ll get an error because the kext only allows one connection. This error is surfaced to the user, which is confusing. We should not connect to the kext unless we need to."</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Default to main and then master</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/super-linter/issues/698</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Is your feature request related to a problem? Please describe.</strong>rnrnFollowing the guidance of github, many developers are moving to <code>main</code> as their default branch. Saving developers from the very small hindrance of using <code>DEFAULT_BRANCH: main</code> would contribute to smoothing the transition.rnrn<strong>Describe the solution you’d like</strong>rnrnThe default branch should be <code>main</code>. If it does not exist, use <code>master</code>, given that many repositories will continue using this name."</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Support linting infrastructure-as-code descriptors with Checkov</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/super-linter/issues/694</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Is your feature request related to a problem? Please describe.</strong>rnhttps://github.com/bridgecrewio/checkov is a tool to check infrastructure-as-code descriptors. <code>It scans cloud infrastructure provisioned using Terraform, Cloudformation, Kubernetes, Serverless or ARM Templates and detects security and compliance misconfigurations.</code>rnrn<strong>Describe the solution you’d like</strong>rnSupport <code>checkov</code>.rnrn<strong>Describe alternatives you’ve considered</strong>rnN/Arnrn<strong>Additional context</strong>rnN/Arnrn<strong>Note</strong>rnIf this is a request to add a new language, after submitting this issue check out <a href="https://github.com/github/super-linter/wiki/Adding-new-language-support">the wiki</a> for more info on how to accomplish that.rn"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Support scanning Terraform with tfsec</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/super-linter/issues/693</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Is your feature request related to a problem? Please describe.</strong>rnhttps://github.com/liamg/tfsec is a popular (more than TerraScan at least!) security-oriented linter for Terraform.rnrn<strong>Describe the solution you’d like</strong>rnSupport tfsec as one of the linters that super-linter ships.rnrn<strong>Describe alternatives you’ve considered</strong>rnN/Arnrn<strong>Additional context</strong>rnN/Arnrn<strong>Note</strong>rnIf this is a request to add a new language, after submitting this issue check out <a href="https://github.com/github/super-linter/wiki/Adding-new-language-support">the wiki</a> for more info on how to accomplish that.rn"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Bazel Support</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/super-linter/issues/393</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>bazel linterrnrn- <a href="https://github.com/bazelbuild/buildtools/blob/master/buildifier/README.md">buildifier</a>"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Scala Support</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/super-linter/issues/392</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Scala linter support.rnrnChoices arern- <a href="https://github.com/scalacenter/scalafix">scalafix</a>rn- <a href="https://github.com/scalameta/scalafmt">scalafmt</a>rn- <a href="https://github.com/scalastyle/scalastyle">scalastyle</a>rn- <a href="https://github.com/wartremover/wartremover">wartremover</a>"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Scala Support</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/super-linter/issues/392</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Scala linter support.rnrnChoices arern- <a href="https://github.com/scalacenter/scalafix">scalafix</a>rn- <a href="https://github.com/scalameta/scalafmt">scalafmt</a>rn- <a href="https://github.com/scalastyle/scalastyle">scalastyle</a>rn- <a href="https://github.com/wartremover/wartremover">wartremover</a>"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Prettier for JavaScript and TypeScript</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/super-linter/issues/175</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>IIUC, super-linter uses ESLint and Standard to format JavaScript and TypeScript code rather than Prettier. I think many developers will have an issue with this. Despite the name, Standard is not a standard. It’s developers just gave it that name. For the past few years the trend has been to use ESLint only to check for issues and to use Prettier for formatting.rnrnMost developers will be fine with most of the formatting that Standard performs. However, there is one controversial thing that it does. It enforces a space after function names in their definition. For example:rnrn<code>jsrnfunction myName (param1, param2) {rn  ...rn)rn</code>rnrnI think you will find that almost no JavaScript developer does this. So using Standard will make this change across their code bases and they will not like it.rnrnPlease reconsider the use of Standard for JavaScript formatting and instead use Prettier, which is by far the more popular option.rn"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Make previews controller extensible </title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/view_component/issues/434</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <h2 id="feature-requestrnrnmake-the-previews-controller-to-be-extensible-by-allowing-users-to-add-authentication-authorization-before-actions-or-anything-that-the-end-user-would-need-to-meet-their-needs.-rnrn-motivationrnit-all-started-in-discussion-412-rnjonspalmer-came-up-with-a-good-suggestion-which-is-to-copy-devises-parent-class-feature.-it-will-enable-devs-to-set-up-a-parent-class-if-needed.-rnrnhttpsgithub.comgithubview_componentdiscussions412discussioncomment-41084rnrn">Feature requestrn<!-- Provide a summary of the behavior. -->rnMake the previews controller to be extensible by allowing users to add authentication, authorization, before actions, or anything that the end user would need to meet their needs. rnrn### MotivationrnIt all started in discussion #412 rn@jonspalmer came up with a good suggestion, which is to copy Devise’s “parent class” feature. It will enable devs to set up a parent class if needed. rnrnhttps://github.com/github/view_component/discussions/412#discussioncomment-41084rn<!-- What would you like to do with this feature? Can you providerncontext or references to similar behavior in other libraries? -->rn"</h2> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>ActiveSupport::Notifications instrumentation</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/view_component/issues/427</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <h2 id="feature-requestrnhave-activesupportnotifications-instrumentation.rnrn-motivationrnrnit-may-be-nice-to-have-some-information-about-time-used-to-render-the-component.-like-actionview-does-in-developer-server-logs.rnrnexamplesrn--simple-component-rendering-rendered-buttoncomponent-duration-1.2ms-allocations-123rn--collection-rendering-rendered-collection-of-buttoncomponent-10-times-duration-1.2ms-allocations-123rnrnrnstarted-get-postsaa147930-7749-4d52-a44b-29548e093447edit-for-127.0.0.1-at-2020-07-29-010919-0200rnprocessing-by-postscontrolleredit-as-htmlrn-parameters-idaa147930-7749-4d52-a44b-29548e093447rn-post-load-2.0ms-select-posts.-from-posts-where-posts.id-1-limit-2-id-aa147930-7749-4d52-a44b-29548e093447-limit-1rn-appcontrollersposts_controller.rb51in-set_postrn-rendering-postsedit.html.slim-within-layoutsapplicationrn-rendered-buttoncomponent-duration-1.2ms-allocations-123rn-rendered-posts_form.html.slim-duration-6.3ms-allocations-3331rn-rendered-postsedit.html.slim-within-layoutsapplication-duration-9.4ms-allocations-5561rncompleted-200-ok-in-46ms-views-26.1ms-activerecord-2.3ms-allocations-19197rnrn">Feature requestrnHave <code>ActiveSupport::Notifications</code> instrumentation.rnrn### MotivationrnrnIt may be nice to have some information about time used to render the component. Like <code>ActionView</code> does in developer server logs.rnrnExamples:rn- simple component rendering <code>Rendered ButtonComponent (Duration: 1.2ms | Allocations: 123)</code>rn- collection rendering <code>Rendered collection of ButtonComponent [10 times] (Duration: 1.2ms | Allocations: 123)</code>rnrn<code>rnStarted GET "/posts/aa147930-7749-4d52-a44b-29548e093447/edit" for 127.0.0.1 at 2020-07-29 01:09:19 +0200rnProcessing by PostsController#edit as HTMLrn  Parameters: {"id"=&gt;"aa147930-7749-4d52-a44b-29548e093447"}rn  Post Load (2.0ms)  SELECT "posts".* FROM "posts" WHERE "posts"."id" = $1 LIMIT $2  [["id", "aa147930-7749-4d52-a44b-29548e093447"], ["LIMIT", 1]]rn  ↳ app/controllers/posts_controller.rb:51:in `set_post'rn  Rendering posts/edit.html.slim within layouts/applicationrn  Rendered ButtonComponent (Duration: 1.2ms | Allocations: 123)rn  Rendered posts/_form.html.slim (Duration: 6.3ms | Allocations: 3331)rn  Rendered posts/edit.html.slim within layouts/application (Duration: 9.4ms | Allocations: 5561)rnCompleted 200 OK in 46ms (Views: 26.1ms | ActiveRecord: 2.3ms | Allocations: 19197)rn</code>rn"</h2> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Access request within SlotComponent instance</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/view_component/issues/409</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <h2 id="feature-requestrnhttpsgithub.comgithubview_componentpull59-added-context-and-access-to-the-request-object-within-the-component-however-this-does-not-seem-to-extend-to-slotcomponent.rni-would-like-to-propose-this-change-to-slotcomponents-also-rnrn-motivationrnrni-would-like-to-use-an-active-nav-anchor-tag-in-a-navitem-slot-within-a-navbarcomponent-by-using-the-request-to-determine-the-current_page-currently-i-having-to-work-around-this-by-wrapping-the-slotcomponent-instance-in-a-method-in-the-parent-component-and-calling-the-method-from-the-template.rnto-me-the-slotcomponents-should-have-access-to-the-same-helpers-and-view-context-that-the-parent-components-currently-provide.rnrni-will-attempt-a-pr-of-this-myself-if-theres-acceptance-and-motivation-to-do-so.">Feature requestrnhttps://github.com/github/view_component/pull/59 added context and access to the request object within the component, however this does not seem to extend to SlotComponent.rnI would like to propose this change to SlotComponents also rnrn### MotivationrnrnI would like to use an active nav anchor tag in a NavItem slot within a NavBarComponent, by using the request to determine the <code>current_page?</code> Currently I having to work around this by wrapping the SlotComponent instance in a method in the parent Component and calling the method from the template.rnTo me the SlotComponents should have access to the same helpers and view context that the parent components currently provide.rnrnI will attempt a PR of this myself if there’s acceptance and motivation to do so. "</h2> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Add failing tests for rendering with layouts</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/view_component/pull/395</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <!-- See https://github.com/github/view_component/blob/master/CONTRIBUTING.md#submitting-a-pull-request  -->
<p>rnrn### Summaryrnrn<!-- Provide a general description of the code changes in your pullrnrequest... were there any bugs you had fixed? If so, mention them. Ifrnthese bugs have open GitHub issues, be sure to tag them here as well,rnto keep the conversation linked together. -->rnThis is a merge request for discussing a possible API for implementing #391 rnrnI would have liked to have layouts included by default with <code>render</code>. I would understand if that is deemed an API break and a alternative needs to be determined.rnrnAdditionally, I have added a test that checks the view context is shared between the layout and the component.rnrn### Other Informationrnrn<!-- If there's anything else that's important and relevant to your pullrnrequest, mention that information here. This could includernbenchmarks, or other information.rnrnIf you are updating any of the CHANGELOG files or are asked to update thernCHANGELOG files by reviewers, please add the CHANGELOG entry at the top of the file. -->rn"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Support multiple views</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/view_component/issues/387</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <h2 id="feature-requestrnrnrnallow-refactoring-small-view-parts-into-a-separate-view-and-be-able-to-render-them-into-the-template.-these-views-should-not-be-available-outside-the-component.rnrnrnappcomponentsmy_componentmy_component.html.erbrnappcomponentsmy_componenta_part.html.erbrnrnrnerbrn-my_component.html.erb-rn-render-a_part-rnrnrn-motivationrnrnrnrnsometimes-it-is-useful-to-separate-a-sub-component-from-the-component.-for-example-if-i-want-to-render-a-popover-with-extra-info-about-a-particular-model-i-would-want-to-extract-that-popover-into-a-separate-view.-rnrnalternative-solutionsrnrn1.-extract-a-new-component.-because-the-popover-is-not-a-generic-one-to-be-used-in-other-parts-of-the-application-it-doesnt-make-much-sense-to-create-a-now-public-component-for-it.rn2.-use-content_for.-this-is-not-suitable-if-the-partial-needs-to-take-arguments.-in-my-example-it-wouldnt-work-if-im-displaying-a-list-of-models-and-i-want-to-show-the-popover-for-each-model.rnrnprior-artrnactionview-does-support-partials-of-course.rncells-does-allow-multiple-views-per-cell-and-allows-using-render-view-a_part.rnrn-possible-solutions-i-seernrn1.-provide-a-method-that-prefixes-the-component-dir-and-then-goes-on-to-call-render-template-with-the-full-path.-i-would-suspect-this-is-relatively-slow-given-that-render-is-slow-in-actionview.-rn2.-precompile-all-the-templates-into-methods-with-a-reserved-prefix-and-allow-calling-them-from-the-view.-for-example-using-extra_views_view_name.rnrn">Feature requestrn<!-- Provide a summary of the behavior. -->rnrnAllow refactoring small view parts into a separate view, and be able to <code>render</code> them into the template. These views should not be available outside the component.rnrn<code>rnapp/components/my_component/my_component.html.erbrnapp/components/my_component/a_part.html.erbrn</code>rnrn<code>erbrn&lt;<item>	<title>Fix rendering of components that utilize `capture` in a parent view context</title>
	<link>https://github.com/github/view_component/pull/240</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>In Rails, when you create a form it saves a reference to the currentrntemplate object that is rendering the form. When you render a formrnbuilder helper method, like <code>form.label</code> inside of a child component therntemplate object will be the original template object from where the formrnbuilder was instantiated.rnrnThis means in cases where we pass a block to a form builder helper thern<code>@output_buffer</code> is the parent component’s output buffer. So when thatrnbuffer is overridden via <code>.capture</code> it’s setting the parent component’srn<code>@output_buffer</code> to a new, temporary buffer but it doesn’t change thernchild component that is actually rendering’s <code>@output_buffer</code>. Thisrnmeans the block is executed in the context of the child componentsrnactual <code>@output_buffer</code> and immediately writes to the buffer. Sincern<code>capture</code> had nothing written to the temporary buffer, it returns thernvalue of the block call and then inserts that into the parentrncomponent’s <code>@output_buffer</code>.rnrnThis resolves the issue by monkey patching <code>ActionView::Base</code> to supportrna new <code>child_component</code> attribute and overriding <code>output_buffer=</code> to setrnits <code>child_component</code>s output_buffer to whatever <code>output_buffer</code> is setrnto. With that in place, when <code>capture</code> is called, then #output_buffer=`rnis called which will update the child component’s output buffer to the new rntemporary buffer correctly."</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>OSD level scale invisible</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ubuntu/yaru/issues/2214</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Hi there, first of all, thanks for this very nice theme.rnrnI’m using Yaru 20.04 on openSUSE Tumbleweed and Leap 15.2 with Mate 1.24.0. There is a problem where the OSD horizontal fine-grained level/scale is invisible. Maybe some code could be borrowed from Numix, as it looks perfect under Numix.rnrn————–rnrnYaru (light and normal all behave the same):rnrn<img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/2692138/85305326-880c4b80-b472-11ea-8d15-98d63fb4b3c6.png" alt="Screenshot at 2020-06-22 10-14-21" />rnrn———————rnrnNumix:rnrn<img src="https://user-images.githubusercontent.com/2692138/85305349-90fd1d00-b472-11ea-9db7-e0e1611c0b26.png" alt="Screenshot at 2020-06-22 10-14-35" />rn"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>[Bionic] Check mark (✓) is invisible in Firefox context menu</title>
	<link>https://github.com/ubuntu/yaru/issues/2064</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <h3 id="steps-to-see-the-issuern1.-open-firefox-and-go-to-a-text-fieldrn2.-right-click-in-a-text-field-and-select-check-spellingrn3.-you-should-see-a-check-mark-beside-check-spellingrn4.-the-check-mark-is-invisiblernrn-software-that-presents-the-issuern--os-ubuntu-18.04rn--app-firefoxrn--version-74rnrn-yaru-versionrn-snap-info-communithemernsnap-id-yd6cispif6tef3zej0cqsoeg9rg2vkrirntracking-latestedgernrefresh-date-11-days-ago-at-1912-cetrnchannelsrn-stable-0.1-2019-03-13-1768-16mb--rn-candidate-rn-beta-rn-edge-29.180-2020-03-03-1970-18mb--rninstalled-29.180-1970-18mb--rn">Steps to see the issuern1. Open Firefox and go to a text fieldrn2. Right-click in a text field and select “Check Spelling”rn3. You should see a check mark (✓) beside “Check Spelling”rn4. The check mark is invisiblernrn### Software that presents the issuern- OS: Ubuntu 18.04rn- App: Firefoxrn- Version: 74rnrn### Yaru versionrn$ snap info communithemernsnap-id: Yd6CISPIf6tEf3ZEJ0cqSoEg9rG2VkRirntracking: latest/edgernrefresh-date: 11 days ago, at 19:12 CETrnchannels:rn stable: 0.1 2019-03-13 (1768) 16MB -rn candidate: ↑ rn beta: ↑ rn edge: 29.180 2020-03-03 (1970) 18MB -rninstalled: 29.180 (1970) 18MB -rn"</h3> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Expose Hot Words into binaries</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/DeepSpeech/issues/3336</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>This is a follow-up of #3297: new API entry points have been added and exposed in all bindings.rnrnThis bug is about replicating what has been done in #3297 for using this new API in the Python binary and do that in all our other binaries, as well as add CI testing:rn - JavaScript (NodeJS, ElectronJS)rn - Java (APK app)rn - .NetrnrnAnyone willing to take care of that is welcome to ask more details, here or on Matrix. This is a good way to get into the project: it’s technically easy but it touches several places as well as CI testing, so you get a nice overview of the surface."</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Please add citation information</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/DeepSpeech/issues/3323</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>rnA <code>CITATION.txt</code> with a BibTeX (ideally a DOI) would be much appreciated :)rnrnSee here for a guideline on how to make code citable:rnhttps://guides.github.com/activities/citable-code/"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Moving away from TaskCluster</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/DeepSpeech/issues/3317</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>TaskCluster is a CI service provided by Mozilla, and available to both Firefox development (Firefox-CI instance) and Community on Github (Community TaskCluster). It’s being widely used across some Mozilla projects, and it has its own advantages. In our case, the control over tasks, over workers for specific needs and long build time was easier to achieve working with the TaskCluster team rather than relying on other CI services.rnrnHowever, this has lead to the CI code being very specific to the project, and kind of a source of frustration for non employees trying to send patches and get involved in the project ; specifically because some of the CI parts were “hand-crafted” and triggering builds and tests requires being a “collaborator” on the Github project, which has other implications making it complicated to enable it easily to anyone. In the end, this creates an artificial barrier to contributing to this project, even though we happily run PRs manually, it is still frustrating for everyone. The issue https://github.com/mozilla/DeepSpeech/issues/3228 was an attempt to fix that, but we came to the conclusion it would be more beneficial for everyone to switch to some well known CI service and setup that is less intimidating. While TaskCluster is a great tool and has helped us a lot, we feel its limitations now makes it inappropriate for the project to stimulate and enable external contributions.rnrnWe would like to take this opportunity to also enable more contributors to hack and own the code related to CI, so discussion is open.rn"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Debug builds on CI</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/DeepSpeech/issues/3292</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>.Net Standard lib in the nuget package</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/DeepSpeech/issues/3285</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Will you add the .Net Standard library into nuget package?"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Memory Leak using Java Native Client</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/DeepSpeech/issues/3271</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>For support and discussions, please use our <a href="https://discourse.mozilla.org/c/mozilla-voice-stt">Discourse forums</a>.rnrnIf you’ve found a bug, or have a feature request, then please create an issue with the following information:rnrn- <strong>Have I written custom code (as opposed to running examples on an unmodified clone of the repository)</strong>:rn- <strong>OS Platform and Distribution (e.g., Linux Ubuntu 16.04)</strong>: Android R (API 30)rn- <strong>Exact command to reproduce</strong>:rnrnI modified the STT-example in Kotlin for use in a Mozilla-STT React Native module I’m building. However, running streaming transcription uses more and more memory until the app crashes. See a fully working example by cloning <a href="https://github.com/zaptrem/react-native-transcription">this repo</a>, running <code>yarn bootstrap</code>, then <code>yarn example android</code>. Attach to it using the Android Studio profiler to watch the memory usage creep upwards. rnrnImplementation: https://github.com/zaptrem/react-native-transcription/blob/master/android/src/main/java/com/reactnativetranscription/TranscriptionModule.ktrnrnrnrnPlease describe the problem clearly. Be sure to convey here why it’s a bug or a feature request.rnrnInclude any logs or source code that would be helpful to diagnose the problem. For larger logs, link to a Gist, not a screenshot. If including tracebacks, please include the full traceback. Try to provide a reproducible test case.rn"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Change Alphabet::EncodeSingle and Alphabet::DecodeSingle to use an outparam and return an error code instead of calling `abort`</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/DeepSpeech/issues/3175</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>I run into the error “Invalid label 0”. I assume it is from the function <code>Alphabet::DecodeSingle()</code> in the file <code>native_client/alphabet.cc</code>.rnrnI don’t know why I am running into this error and it is not important for now. What is important is the fact that the code calls <code>abort()</code> just after printing this error.rnrnI don’t know your guidelines. But I can tell that aborting the whole process, including the python interpreter which might be interactive, is a terrible way of handling errors, especially in such a trivial function, and I call it a bug."</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>No working download links found for ds_ctcdecoder==training/deepspeech_training/VERSION</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/DeepSpeech/issues/3099</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Hello,rnrnwhen I trie to use the <code>setup.py</code> on from <code>version 0.7.4</code> it always calls this error: rnrn<code>No local packages or working download links found for ds_ctcdecoder==training/deepspeech_training/VERSION error: rnCould not find suitable distribution for Requirement.parse('ds_ctcdecoder==training/deepspeech_training/VERSION')</code>rnrnWith the <code>version 0.7.3</code> and older it finds the ds_ctcdecoder but always calls that I need <code>numpy</code> in <code>version 1.16</code>, when I install 1.16 it calls me that I need <code>numpy 1.13.3</code> because of other modules and so on. That’s why I think my only chance to use DeepSpeech is with the newest version.rnrnI’m on windwos 10 with python 3.6.rnrnThanks in advance!rnrnrn"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Add progress bars to transcribe.py</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/DeepSpeech/issues/2985</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>it would be nice to have 2 progress barsrnrn1) transcribing individual files in a dirrn2) transcribing long audio file after VAD split"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Add code coverage report to CI</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/DeepSpeech/issues/2977</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>getting very bad transcript while live streaming on r0.6 version node js socket api</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/DeepSpeech-examples/issues/66</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Hi,rnI have trained my custom model DeepSpeech 0.6.1 on my own data from scratch.rnrnI have getting good accuracy while inference using deepspeech binary (testing wer: 0.18).rnrnWhen i try r0.6 node js socket api and also mic vad streaming using my own data and lm, I am getting very bad transcript.rnrnIt does not capture any word, it just give me an output of same garbage word for each and every spoken word.rnrnMy predicted transcripts:rnrnhaanrnhaan haanrnhaan haan haan …rnrnI saved recorded audio and listen it was of very good quality and when i infer trans from deepspeech binary using the command:rndeepspeech –model model_path –lm lm_path –trie trie_path –audio audio_pathrnrnIt gives me very good transcripts.rnrnSo I am not able to understand why this happens with r0.6.rnwhen I test with 0.5.1 model example of mic vad streaming, then I am getting good accuracy.rnrnCan anyone help me to resolve this.rnWhy I am getting bad transcript on r0.6 node js socket api as well as mic vad streaming.rnrnrnrnThanks"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Windows 10:- mic_vad_streaming.py exited without error and without expected output</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/DeepSpeech-examples/issues/59</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Even though, I have all the dependencies mentioned in requirements, mic_vad_streaming.py didn’t executed properly. Not sure why this happened, I am a beginner please help. Thanks.rn<strong>I used this command:-</strong>rnpython mic_vad_streaming.py -m deepspeech-0.7.3-models.pbmm -s deepspeech-0.7.3-models.scorerrn<strong>Got this output on command line without any errors:-</strong>rnInitializing model…rnINFO:root:ARGS.model: deepspeech-0.7.3-models.pbmmrnTensorFlow: v1.15.0-24-gceb46aae58rnDeepSpeech: v0.7.3-0-g88584941rn2020-06-14 15:59:26.545446: I tensorflow/core/platform/cpu_feature_guard.cc:142] Your CPU supports instructions that this TensorFlow binary was not compiled to use: AVX2rnINFO:root:ARGS.scorer: deepspeech-0.7.3-models.scorerrnrn(newdsvenv) C:_vad_streaming&gt;"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>NodeJS Microphone VAD Streaming - cannot start server</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/DeepSpeech-examples/issues/30</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Hi.rnAfter I run node start.js , nothing happened.rnDo i need to specify to specific port first?rnIf so, can I use socketio protocol, to send the transcribed text over to client?"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Add support for Azure tests</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/frost/issues/312</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>It would be nice to have Azure tests available as we make further use of it.rnrnCan refer to the <a href="https://www.cisecurity.org/benchmark/azure/">CIS Benchmark for Azure</a>, our internal review, and <a href="https://github.com/nccgroup/ScoutSuite/tree/master/ScoutSuite/providers/azure/rules/findings">ScoutSuite’s rules</a> to determine an initial list of tests to add."</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Command table should contain short command names</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/OpenWPM/issues/684</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>It shouldn’t be the full type name in the table but so instead of automation.commands…GetCommand"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Multi-Speaker TTS with Attentron</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/TTS/issues/516</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Attentron is a new method proposed recently and looks like an easy alternation over our current Tacotron2 to enable easier multi-speaker TTS. rnrnpaper: https://arxiv.org/pdf/2005.08484.pdf rnsamples: https://hyperconnect.github.io/Attentron/rnrnRaise hands if you are willing to take this. "</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Train a better Speaker Encoder</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/TTS/issues/512</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Our current <strong>speaker encoder</strong> is trained with only LibriTTS (100, 360) datasets. However, we can improve its performance using other available datasets (VoxCeleb, LibriTTS-500, Common Voice etc.). It will also increase the performance of<a href="https://colab.research.google.com/drive/1OX2jtyxmeFt7kRO65QgPy65ku6HWUrFK?usp=sharing">our multi-speaker model</a> and makes it easier to adapt to new voices. rnrnI can’t really work on this alone due to the recent changes and the amount of work needed therefore <strong>I need some hand</strong> here to work together. rnrnSo I can list the TODO as follows and feel free to contribute to any part of it or suggest changes;rnrn- [x] decide target datasetsrn- [x] download and preprocess the datasetsrn- [x] write preprocessors for new datasetsrn- [x] increase the efficiency of the speaker encoder data-loader.rn- [x] training a model only using Eng datasets.rn- [ ] training a model with all the available datasets. rn "</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>[Feature Request]Android app</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/TTS/issues/506</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>[HELP] Share your trained TTS models?</title>
	<link>https://github.com/mozilla/TTS/issues/395</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p>Please consider sharing your pre-trained models in any language (If the licenses allow that). We can include them in our model catalog for public use by referencing your name (website, company etc.). rnrnThat would enable more people experiment together and coordinate, instead of individual efforts to achieve similar goals. That is also a good chance to make your work more visible.rn "</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Can't load  pxrUSD.mll and AL_USDMayaTestPlugin</title>
	<link>https://github.com/Autodesk/maya-usd/issues/747</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Describe the issue</strong>rnrnAfter I finish the maya-usd instalation, I add as enviroment variables MAYA_MODULE_PATH: D:-usdand Tried to load all plugins from Plugin Manager and I get the following errors rnrn** Script Editor<strong>rn“# Error: file: C:/Program Files/Autodesk/Maya2020/scripts/others/pluginWin.mel line 317: ImportError: file <maya console> line 1: No module named UsdMaya # rn// Error: file: C:/Program Files/Autodesk/Maya2020/scripts/others/pluginWin.mel line 317: initializePlugin function failed (pxrUsd) //”rnrn// Error: file: C:/Program Files/Autodesk/Maya2020/scripts/others/pluginWin.mel line 317: Unable to dynamically load : D:/USD/maya-usd/install/RelWithDebInfo/plugin/al/plugin/AL_USDMayaTestPlugin.mllrnError en una rutina de inicialización de biblioteca de vínculos dinámicos (DLL).rn // rn// Error: file: C:/Program Files/Autodesk/Maya2020/scripts/others/pluginWin.mel line 317: Error en una rutina de inicialización de biblioteca de vínculos dinámicos (DLL).rn (AL_USDMayaTestPlugin) // rnrn</strong>Output Widnow<strong>rnerror detected in .....cpp at line 132rn: (kFailure): Unexpected Internal FailurernCoding Error: in Define at line 150 of D:.cpp – Multiple definitions of TfEnvSetting variable detected. This is usually due to software misconfiguration. Contact the build team for assistance. (duplicate ‘PIXMAYA_ENABLE_BOUNDING_BOX_MODE’)rnCoding Error: in Define at line 150 of D:.cpp – Multiple definitions of TfEnvSetting variable detected. This is usually due to software misconfiguration. Contact the build team for assistance. (duplicate ‘PIXMAYA_USE_USD_ASSEM_NAMESPACE’)rnrnAPI error detected in .....cpp at line 132rn: (kFailure): Unexpected Internal Failurernrnrn// Error: file: C:/Program Files/Autodesk/Maya2020/scripts/others/pluginWin.mel line 317: initializePlugin function failed (AL_USDMayaTestPlugin) rnrnrnAPI error detected in .....cpp at line 132rn: (kFailure): Unexpected Internal Failurernrnrn</strong>Build log<strong>rnrnrnrnrnrn</strong>Specs:<strong>rn - OS &amp; version Windows 10rn - Compiler &amp; version [e.g. gcc 6.3.1]rn - Maya version Maya 2020rnrn</strong>Additional context**rnAdd any other context about the problem here.rn"</p> ]]></description>
</item>
<item>	<title>Not sure im going the stage test correctly</title>
	<link>https://github.com/Autodesk/maya-usd/issues/705</link>
	<description><![CDATA[ <p><strong>Describe the bug</strong>rnPlease See attatched txt file. I am trying to run my build with –stage=test like this:rn<code>python build.py --maya-location /usr/autodesk/maya2021 --pxrusd-location $SCRIPT_DIR/USD --devkit-location $SCRIPT_DIR/maya_devkit/devkitBase --stages=test  $SCRIPT_DIR/WorkspaceRefractor</code>rnalas it doesn’t do the test, looks pretty unhappy. Not sure whats up.rnrn<strong>Attachments</strong>rn<a href="https://github.com/Autodesk/maya-usd/files/5057146/build_log.txt">build_log.txt</a>rnrnrn<strong>Specs (if applicable):</strong>rn - OS &amp; version [Linux centos 7.7]rn - Compiler &amp; version [ gcc 6.3.1]rn - Maya version [Maya 2021/Maya beta PR117]rn - Maya USD commit SHA [ dev at 6210a2a]rn - Pixar USD commit SHA [20.08]rnrn<strong>Additional context</strong>rnFirst time trying this in awhile has never worked for me before. Any help would be appreciated.rnSue rn"</p> ]]></description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
